{
    "id": "18d84d43a205412796024ad570e4ef43",
    "title": "Tenses Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We ……………………………….. here for two hours.",
            "description": "Use the present perfect continuous tense to talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present and is still continuing. ",
            "answers": [
                "are waiting",
                "have been waiting",
                "wait"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c68b9eb69894628901ab7532594ddd6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. to the movies once a month.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about habits, routines etc.",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "am going",
                "have gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "682cb5fa4fb24a98a7524eaaf2d109e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train …………………………… the station at",
            "description": "Left is the past simple and past perfect form of leave. ",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "leaved",
                "has leaved"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6780d79eaaa341b2bd66e2380684ec12"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………….. a few miles away from the railway station.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about permanent arrangements like living places. ",
            "answers": [
                "is living",
                "has lived",
                "lives"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "21fb8b050f824560bbc9d58aa2132ab5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The road to the left ……………………………… to his house.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "leads",
                "is leading",
                "leds"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd210015b6b04970a2d120136a2b1b39"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. here for two weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "am",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dbb3480c072f41d88fbaec010bbab4cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………….. in Mexico.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was born",
                "is born",
                "born"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00a3c9eb83c7497691c037bb22276de0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train …………………………. early in the morning.",
            "description": "The simple present is used to talk about future events that are part of a time table. ",
            "answers": [
                "arrives",
                "is arriving",
                "arrive"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d616a371c3e44a41b65de8d5edfe09a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The weather …………………………… good today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has",
                "is being"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "48ec0203342a4ec2aada209bf905f738"
        },
        {
            "question": "The students …………………………….. on a picnic yesterday.",
            "description": "The present perfect cannot be used with past time expressions.",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "has been",
                "has gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc082b7a6fa94e2b8a87eec38c727067"
        },
        {
            "question": "I first ……………………………… her in a park.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "meet",
                "have met"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6a41d3c1d44a449a8993a2aa6a9a71bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… English really well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speak",
                "speaks",
                "is speaking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b7e5f6652c5345a39e06b55458d3e4d4"
        }
    ]
}